---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_list_attendees?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&id=5441375300&page=0&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:00:24 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Content-Length:
      - '1872'
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      Vary:
      - Accept-Encoding
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D2%26i%3D29f8cca3-1ff8-4027-94ce-6439d8f320e2%26a%3D670%26s%3D249cce688bbfb8fce309cfa417208193819d37cf;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016 14:00:24 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbblk2uqLaLTjaEdgDk9BxCoKTazqjzIM8jGb02cdSF6xhCUhFdUhEcmeMtd1W7RCqTBTnDi5OxHIZLUr-aDEoYgNMh39vd6K8MCHq7JpUsuw70Xo00dQzKJtd14rAeJYkzjWxL8e1vxK43vrtmDQzFPngE-d_NHxedkAuFLbAgixdoSsvo6JbXdTQIyGnpeqP5FkRJOy7sa33fS61Z5bLnvv_Nlu5TECEDi0pAmkQEnBc2ANN_A;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHSaLAVrr6ORe9DKjm8fGfHdFohJMA; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - ebEventToTrack=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016
        14:00:24 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016 14:00:24 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016 14:00:24 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
    body:
      encoding: ASCII-8BIT
      string: '{"attendees": [{"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Fish",
        "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20",
        "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181778452, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type":
        "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog":
        "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address":
        "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id": 142052968, "company":
        "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142052968181778452001", "answers": [{"answer":
        {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question": "Billing Address (line
        1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line 2)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "London", "question":
        "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518682}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing Address
        (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question": "Billing Address
        (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "01234 5678910",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question": "VAT reg number
        (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        01:20:27", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "modified": "2014-05-30 05:39:54", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone":
        "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456,
        "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country":
        "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181785692, "first_name":
        "Bob", "order_type": "PayPal Completed", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "",
        "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address":
        "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id": 142059188, "company":
        "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142059188181785692001", "answers": [{"answer":
        {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question": "Billing Address (line
        1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line 2)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "London", "question":
        "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518682}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing Address
        (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question": "Billing Address
        (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "01234 5678910",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question": "VAT reg number
        (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        02:20:48", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "modified": "2014-05-30 05:41:47", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone":
        "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 37192603,
        "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country":
        "GB", "tax": "40.00", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 551569614, "first_name":
        "Bob", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date":
        "", "eventbrite_fee": "5.65", "amount_paid": "245.65", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        436351985, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "436351985551569614001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2015-07-01
        04:46:15", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "modified": "2015-07-01 04:48:33", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone":
        "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 37192604,
        "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country":
        "GB", "tax": "60.00", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 551572443, "first_name":
        "Bob", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date":
        "", "eventbrite_fee": "6.50", "amount_paid": "366.50", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        436354296, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "436354296551572443001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2015-07-01
        05:00:23", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "modified": "2015-07-01 05:02:41", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone":
        "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456,
        "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country":
        "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181778454, "first_name":
        "Bob", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date":
        "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        142052968, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142052968181778454001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        01:20:27", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "modified": "2014-05-30 05:55:09", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone":
        "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"last_name": "Fish",
        "ship_region": "", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.00", "currency": "GBP",
        "id": 181781836, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "Free Order", "event_id":
        5441375300, "ticket_id": 17042304, "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.00",
        "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "ship_address": "", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142055824, "amount_paid": "0.00", "barcode": "142055824181781836001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector",
        "question_type": "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount":
        "", "created": "2013-02-15 01:49:13", "ship_postal_code": "", "ship_city":
        "", "ship_address_2": "", "modified": "2014-05-30 05:41:32", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "cc_fee": "0.00", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id":
        37154637, "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country":
        "GB", "tax": "20.00", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 551212824, "first_name":
        "Bob", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date":
        "", "eventbrite_fee": "3.15", "amount_paid": "120.00", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        436072182, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "436072182551212824001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2015-06-30
        03:58:14", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "modified": "2015-06-30 04:00:52", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate":
        "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone":
        "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456,
        "last_name": "Miliband", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "West Sussex", "ship_country":
        "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 187690446, "first_name":
        "Ed", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "ed@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date":
        "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        146845618, "company": "Labour Party", "barcode": "146845618187690446001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+finance@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 432435",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234YZ", "question": "Membership
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "PO1234666454", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-03-01 01:04:32",
        "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "modified":
        "2013-07-24 02:18:15", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "+44 1735 324312",
        "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"last_name": "Smith", "ship_region":
        "", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "id": 182609582,
        "first_name": "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received",
        "event_id": 5441375300, "ticket_id": 17042456, "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.68", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk", "ship_address": "", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142722298, "amount_paid": "1.20", "barcode": "142722298182609582001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "West Sussex",
        "question": "Billing Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "question": "Billing Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 105349", "question": "Billing Phone Number",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "XX121342543", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "PO123442", "question": "Purchase Order
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "",
        "created": "2013-02-18 01:25:48", "ship_postal_code": "", "ship_city": "",
        "ship_address_2": "", "modified": "2013-07-24 02:18:16", "affiliate": "",
        "ship_phone": "", "cc_fee": "0.00", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id":
        17042456, "last_name": "Smith", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "West Sussex",
        "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id":
        181804062, "first_name": "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment
        Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142074438, "company": "The ODI", "barcode": "142074438181804062001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "65 Clifton Street", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "-", "question": "Billing Address (line 2)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "London", "question":
        "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518682}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "-", "question": "Billing Address (region)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "No idea", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+billing@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 105349",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "123243", "question": "Purchase Order
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "",
        "created": "2013-02-15 04:34:29", "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender":
        "", "ship_address_2": "", "modified": "2013-02-15 04:35:57", "cc_fee": "0.00",
        "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "",
        "cell_phone": "07715105349", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id":
        17042456, "last_name": "Smith", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "West Sussex",
        "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id":
        182620900, "first_name": "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment
        Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142731672, "company": "Widgets ''r'' us", "barcode": "142731672182620900001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+finance@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 154387",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "ODI45434", "question": "Membership
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "PO453543", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-18 02:51:44",
        "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "modified":
        "2013-02-18 02:54:32", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "07715105349", "age":
        "", "quantity": 1}}]}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:00:25 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_get?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&id=5441375300&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:00:25 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Content-Length:
      - '993'
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      Vary:
      - Accept-Encoding
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D2%26i%3D2f00bcce-7433-4f97-a0bd-76a277a0a945%26a%3D670%26s%3Da8c773b3094cf886c0078b8160b8e61d6a1dd2c2;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016 14:00:25 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbllAajSb73t8_J4CnHOJMPKuIQ_-OQCGNcTXubdGFWYPfz8-6L3-o83E--DAukqxhW8RtrxdAxsZ_uQ7CAb3ucie5sIDEGYvfi9ZGvfCwo5nb3cXnHrYLCU80RXnabBirElzRMXb0uuM-P8ZH9BASEhU7H2j0__Go7tFsHI7FxvPONuKCfvCmhA8TVgOhCmhiTUvzGvhhVal4GutRTAQuog6XU70yEFRG5UFUOGyFkmAdvtYIo;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHRJGB5cp2146PylW1caVsoy2D4XqQ; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - ebEventToTrack=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016
        14:00:25 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016 14:00:25 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Thu, 03-Nov-2016 14:00:25 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
    body:
      encoding: ASCII-8BIT
      string: '{"event": {"box_header_text_color": "005580", "locale": "en_GB", "link_color":
        "EE6600", "box_background_color": "FFFFFF", "box_border_color": "D5D5D3",
        "timezone": "Europe/London", "organizer": {"url": "http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/o/odi-tech-<EVENTBRITE_ORGANIZER_ID>",
        "description": "", "long_description": "Just here for the testing...", "id":
        <EVENTBRITE_ORGANIZER_ID>, "name": "ODI Tech"}, "background_color": "FFFFFF",
        "id": 5441375300, "category": "", "box_header_background_color": "EFEFEF",
        "capacity": 0, "num_attendee_rows": 11, "title": "[Test Event 00] Drupal:
        Down the Rabbit Hole", "start_date": "2020-06-17 19:00:00", "status": "Live",
        "description": "\u003cP\u003eThis is the description.\u003c/P\u003e", "end_date":
        "2020-06-17 22:00:00", "tags": "", "timezone_offset": "GMT+0100", "text_color":
        "005580", "title_text_color": "", "password": "", "tickets": [{"ticket": {"description":
        "", "end_date": "2013-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null, "price": "0.00",
        "quantity_sold": 1, "visible": "<VCR_DEBUG>", "start_date": "2013-02-11 09:00:00",
        "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available": 100, "display_price": "0.00", "type":
        0, "id": 17042304, "include_fee": "<VCR_DEBUG>", "name": "Free Ticket"}},
        {"ticket": {"description": "", "end_date": "2013-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1,
        "max": null, "price": "1.00", "quantity_sold": 7, "visible": "<VCR_DEBUG>",
        "start_date": "2013-06-13 18:00:00", "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available":
        100, "display_price": "1.00", "type": 0, "id": 17042456, "include_fee": "<VCR_DEBUG>",
        "name": "Cheap Ticket"}}, {"ticket": {"description": "", "end_date": "2015-07-31
        18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null, "price": "100.00", "quantity_sold": 1, "visible":
        "false", "start_date": "2015-06-30 01:25:00", "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available":
        100, "display_price": "100.00", "type": 0, "id": 37154637, "include_fee":
        "<VCR_DEBUG>", "name": "Individual supporter package"}}, {"ticket": {"description":
        "", "end_date": "2020-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null, "price": "205.65",
        "quantity_sold": 1, "visible": "<VCR_DEBUG>", "start_date": "2015-07-01 04:30:00",
        "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available": 200, "display_price": "200.00", "type":
        0, "id": 37192603, "include_fee": "false", "name": "Summit SME package"}},
        {"ticket": {"description": "", "end_date": "2020-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1,
        "max": null, "price": "306.50", "quantity_sold": 1, "visible": "<VCR_DEBUG>",
        "start_date": "2015-07-01 04:30:00", "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available":
        100, "display_price": "300.00", "type": 0, "id": 37192604, "include_fee":
        "false", "name": "Summit platinum corporate package"}}], "created": "2013-02-05
        09:08:12", "url": "https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/test-event-00-drupal-down-the-rabbit-hole-tickets-5441375300?ref=ebapi",
        "box_text_color": "000000", "privacy": "Private", "venue": {"city": "", "name":
        "The office", "country": "", "region": "", "longitude": 31.8087, "postal_code":
        "", "address_2": "", "address": "", "latitude": -1.2224, "country_code": "",
        "id": 2959410, "Lat-Long": "-1.2224 / 31.8087"}, "modified": "2015-09-01 04:32:23",
        "repeats": "no"}}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Wed, 04 Nov 2015 14:00:27 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 2.9.3
